A Guide to the Webb-Smith Family Papers, 1703-1929
Library of Virginia
- Oversize (Box 23, Reel 2719)
  - Paymaster General, War Department, Appropriation, 1823 (Box 23, Folder 16, Reel 2719)
  - Powers of Attorney, 1792, 1846 (Box 23, Folder 17, Reel 2719)
  - Richmond Enquirer (portion), 8 August 1817 (Box 23, Folder 18, Reel 2719)
  - Rules of Court for the Ninth Judicial Circuit of Virginia, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 19, Reel 2719)
  - Schedule of Property of Anderson Jeffries, 1804 (Box 23, Folder 20, Reel 2719)
  - Surveys (Box 23, Folder 21, Reel 2719)
  - Will of William Brooking, Gloucester County, 1703 (Box 23, Folder 22, Reel 2719)